framesdirect.com 2017-09-28

# FramesDirect.com Privacy & Security Policy

## Terms and Conditions 

We collect information from you when you register on our site, order eyeglasses, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * **To personalize your experience**

> Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs. 

  * **To improve our website**

> We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you. 

  * **To improve customer service**

> Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs. 

  * **To process transactions**

> Your information will never be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company, without your consent, for any reason other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service you have requested. We may share your billing information with the external payment service providers we partner with, but only as is necessary for the processing of your payment or to prevent or detect fraud. These companies have agreed not to retain, share, store or use your Personally Identifiable Information which we pass to them for any secondary purposes.   
> 

  * **To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature**

> In some cases, these may require interfacing with third party solutions and software. 

  * **To send periodic emails**

> The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. 

**Note:** If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers. 

Yes. (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. 

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. 

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone. 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

Some of your information may be used by any FramesDirect affiliates (including any entity within the Essilor group) to contact you about sales, new products, special offers, and new site features, unless you have opted to not receive promotional communications. Each email sent to you by our affiliates and / or other companies within our group will include an 'unsubscribe' link. 

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. 

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into the "My Account" section of the site and making the necessary changes themselves. 

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or any of FramesDirect.com's use of your information, please complete the Contact Us form [here](https://www.framesdirect.com/include/information/contactus.aspx "contact us")[](mailto:info@framesdirect.com)

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy. 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on February 12, 2015 

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

> FramesDirect.com   
> 2801 S. I-35, Suite 170   
> Austin, TX 78741   
> USA
